<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>pets on Cleaning Marketplace!</title>
    <link>https://cleaning-marketplace.com/categories/pets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pets on Cleaning Marketplace!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 09:44:40 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cleaning-marketplace.com/categories/pets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning Pet Urine in Carpets</title>
      <link>https://cleaning-marketplace.com/tips/cleaning-pet-urine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 09:44:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cleaning-marketplace.com/tips/cleaning-pet-urine/</guid>
      <description>How to Remove Dog Pee and Other Stains from Carpet — Without Harsh Chemicals No matter how well-trained your dog is, accidents happen: Maybe they release some “excitement pee” when a new friend comes over or they’re sick and have a bout of diarrhea on the rug. Whatever the situation, every pet parent should have a strategy for cleaning up pet urine and poop stains.
This simple, three-step pet stain and urine odor remover uses natural, eco-friendly products that you probably already have in your pantry or cupboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning Pet Hair</title>
      <link>https://cleaning-marketplace.com/tips/cleaning-pet-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 11:33:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cleaning-marketplace.com/tips/cleaning-pet-hair/</guid>
      <description>Remove Pet Hair with Rubber Gloves Pet hair is a common problem with a simple solution As much as we love our four-legged friends, pet hair can be a problem in the houshold, especially for those of us with pet allergies. Skip spending extra money on tools and special attachments and use this simple hack to clean up after your kitties and doggos. Simply wear rubber household gloves and run them over the surface of your furniture, making sure to get in-between couch seats and cushions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
